Nothing is as it seems.
Night of the Reaper is a horror, thriller film directed by Brandon Christensen.
College student Deena visits her hometown and is roped into a babysitting gig.
Meanwhile, the local sheriff, after receiving a piece of evidence in the mail, falls into
an increasingly desperate scavenger hunt involving a series of murders.
Deena, played by Jessica Clement.
Sheriff Rodney Arnold, played by Ryan Robbins.
Emily Golding, played by Summer H. Howell.
Elizabeth Talbot, played by Keegan Connor Tracy.
Officer Butch Cassidy, played by Matty Finochio.
Max Arnold, played by Max Christensen.
Night of the Reaper is a 2025 slasher film directed by Brandon
Christensen, starring Jessica Clement, Ryan Robbins, Summer H.
Howell, Keegan Connor Tracy, Matty Finochi, Max
Christensen, Bryn Samuel and Ben Cockell.
The film follow a woman (Clement) who takes a job as a
babysitter before finding herself being threatened.
Meanwhile, the sheriff (Robbins) obtains a tape
containing footage of previous murders.
The film explores themes of sheriff, babysitter,
murder, slasher, police officer.
The tone is dark and intense.